Guide to the Lewis M. Porter, Class of 1924, Sheffield Scientific School, Yale University, Memorabilia
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Lewis M. Porter, Class of 1924, Sheffield Scientific School, Yale University, memorabilia
1922-1969
RU 402
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
0.75
The memorabilia consists of ephemera, photographs, and a thesis documenting Lewis M. Porter (Yale 1924S) as a student and alumnus of Yale.
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 45 (YRG 45), Yale objects and memorabilia.
Conditions Governing Access
The materials are open for research.
Arrangement
The materials are arranged by accession.
Scope and Contents
The memorabilia consists of ephemera, photographs, and a thesis documenting Lewis M. Porter (Yale 1924S) as a student and alumnus of Yale.
Photographs; Porter, Lewis Morgan; Yale University -- Students
- Memorabilia, 1922-1969; Accession 1999-A-009
  - Theses
    - "The Preliminary Design of a Steam Power Plant for a Modern City", 1925 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - "The Transmission Efficiency of Motor Trucks", 1926 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Photographs
    - Reunions and class dinner, Class of 1924S, 1927-circa 1964 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Yale buildings, Undated (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Individuals, probably classmates, Undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Alumni Weekly clippings and other class notes, 1935-1949 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Class secretary material, 1940-1945 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Yale class book material, 1935-1939 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Memorial dinner, 45threunion, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Personal papers: scholarship reports, Sigma Xi, tobacco pouch, 1922-1926 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Ephemera: Yale Club brochures, Yale stickers, aerial view of campus, 1926-1930 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Class reunion buttons, Undated (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Sheffield Scientific School Class Day booklet, 1924 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Reunion slides, 1949-1964 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Two jackets with college insignia, circa 1924 (Box 3)
- Memorabilia, 1924-1949; Accession 1999-A-033
  - "1924 AC 8c Sheff 15th Reunion, New Haven," 16mm film, 1939 June 17-20 (Box 1)
  - "1925S 25th Reunion," 16mm film, 1949 June 20 (Box 2)
  - Diplomas, 1924-1926 (Box 3)